<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TEC PA &amp; Lighting</title>
    <link>http://www.nottinghamtec.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TEC PA &amp; Lighting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 01:23:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.nottinghamtec.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Committee</title>
      <link>http://www.nottinghamtec.co.uk/committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 01:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nottinghamtec.co.uk/committee/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://www.nottinghamtec.co.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 16:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nottinghamtec.co.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description>General Details  Phone 0115 84 68720 Email info@nottinghamtec.co.uk Emergency Phone  07825 065681
07825 065678   Office Our members regularly spend time in the office, please feel free to pop in and say hi.
 Phone 0115 84 68720 Address TEC PA &amp;amp; Lighting C87 Portland Building University Park University of Nottingham Nottingham NG7 2RD    Storeroom Our storeroom is located on Kings Meadow Campus, a short journey by the 902 University Hopper Bus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://www.nottinghamtec.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nottinghamtec.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>TEC PA &amp;amp; Lighting exists “To provide high quality sound, lighting and audio-visual services to organisations both within and outside the University of Nottingham Students’ Union”. Staffed entirely by student volunteers from the University of Nottingham, we hold a large stock of equipment built up over many years.
TEC have the capability to provide a variety of event production services within the local area, as well as to the University of Nottingham and its Students’ Union.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal</title>
      <link>http://www.nottinghamtec.co.uk/legal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nottinghamtec.co.uk/legal/</guid>
      <description>Website Terms and Conditions Welcome to TEC PA &amp;amp; Lighting. If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern TEC’s relationship with you in relation to this website. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>